<resources>
    <string name="app_name">City Izhevsk</string>
    <string name="city_name">Izhevsk</string>
    <string name="city_tagline">A compact city guide with places to walk, study culture, and spend a free evening.</string>
    <string name="action_open_menu">Open navigation menu</string>
    <string name="action_back">Back</string>
    <string name="nav_home">Home</string>
    <string name="nav_about">About</string>
    <string name="nav_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="drawer_categories">Categories</string>
    <string name="drawer_info">Application</string>
    <string name="home_categories_title">Explore by category</string>
    <string name="about_summary">City Izhevsk is a compact guide to the city’s culture spots, parks, and shopping malls with a navigation drawer, bottom navigation, and a dedicated details screen for each recommendation.</string>
    <string name="detail_about_title">Why visit</string>
    <string name="category_culture">Culture</string>
    <string name="category_culture_description">Museums and stages that help understand the industrial, artistic, and musical character of Izhevsk.</string>
    <string name="category_parks">Parks</string>
    <string name="category_parks_description">Green spaces and long walking routes for a calmer pace inside the city.</string>
    <string name="category_shopping">Shopping Malls</string>
    <string name="category_shopping_description">Large indoor complexes where it is easy to combine shopping, food, cinema, and a short break.</string>
    <string name="settings_theme_title">Dark theme</string>
    <string name="settings_theme_text">Switches the application between light and dark mode.</string>
    <string name="culture_1_title">M.T. Kalashnikov Museum</string>
    <string name="culture_1_description">A key place for learning about the city’s engineering history and the story of the famous designer.</string>
    <string name="culture_1_detail">Start with this museum if you want a concise introduction to Izhevsk’s industrial identity. The exposition usually combines biography, city context, and technology in a way that is easy to follow even on a short visit.</string>
    <string name="culture_2_title">National Museum of the Udmurt Republic</string>
    <string name="culture_2_description">A broad regional collection with archaeology, ethnography, and everyday history.</string>
    <string name="culture_2_detail">Choose this stop when you want more than a city walk. The museum helps place Izhevsk inside the wider culture of Udmurtia and adds context before visiting nearby central landmarks.</string>
    <string name="culture_3_title">Udmurt Republican Museum of Fine Arts</string>
    <string name="culture_3_description">A quieter cultural stop with painting, graphics, and temporary exhibitions.</string>
    <string name="culture_3_detail">This museum works well for a slower itinerary. It suits days when you want to switch from busy streets to a calm interior and spend time with a compact collection.</string>
    <string name="culture_4_title">Russian Drama Theatre of Udmurtia</string>
    <string name="culture_4_description">An evening option for those who want to end the route with a live performance.</string>
    <string name="culture_4_detail">Add the theatre to your plan if you want the city after dark to feel just as full as the daytime walk. A performance here pairs well with a stroll through the central streets beforehand.</string>
    <string name="culture_5_title">State Opera and Ballet Theatre</string>
    <string name="culture_5_description">A formal cultural venue for a more ceremonial city evening.</string>
    <string name="culture_5_detail">This recommendation fits when you want a stronger event feeling rather than a casual stop. The theatre is useful as the final point of a central route with landmarks and dinner nearby.</string>
    <string name="parks_1_title">Dragunov Gunsmith Park</string>
    <string name="parks_1_description">A modern neighborhood park with walking paths, a pond, and a calmer atmosphere.</string>
    <string name="parks_1_detail">Dragunov Gunsmith Park works well for a short and quiet outdoor stop. It fits the parks category more precisely: greenery, paths, water, and an easy local route.</string>
    <string name="parks_2_title">Kirov Park</string>
    <string name="parks_2_description">A familiar city park with trees, rides, and a relaxed daily atmosphere.</string>
    <string name="parks_2_detail">Choose Kirov Park for an easy walk without a complicated plan. It works for both short breaks and longer outings when you want greenery without leaving the city fabric.</string>
    <string name="parks_3_title">Summer Garden</string>
    <string name="parks_3_description">A classic recreation area that is comfortable for seasonal strolling.</string>
    <string name="parks_3_detail">This stop is useful when you want an older park mood and a simple walking route. It pairs well with the nearby center and can fill the middle part of the day.</string>
    <string name="parks_4_title">Tishino Park</string>
    <string name="parks_4_description">A modern eco-park in the Ustinovsky district with walking zones, viewing points, and family-friendly infrastructure.</string>
    <string name="parks_4_detail">Choose Tishino Park when you want a more contemporary outdoor setting with wooden paths, an amphitheater, sports areas, and spaces for children. It works well for a relaxed family walk inside the city.</string>
    <string name="parks_5_title">Cosmonauts Park</string>
    <string name="parks_5_description">A neighborhood park that is convenient for a lighter local route.</string>
    <string name="parks_5_detail">This park works when you want to mix everyday city life with an outdoor stop. It is a practical choice for a simple route without crowds or long transfers.</string>
    <string name="shopping_1_title">Talisman</string>
    <string name="shopping_1_description">A mall format that is convenient when you want stores, food, and a quick pause in one place.</string>
    <string name="shopping_1_detail">Use Talisman for a practical break in the middle of the route. It is well suited for combining everyday errands with coffee and time indoors during colder weather.</string>
    <string name="shopping_2_title">Petrovsky</string>
    <string name="shopping_2_description">A shopping point with a broad daily-use focus.</string>
    <string name="shopping_2_detail">Choose Petrovsky when the route needs a functional stop rather than a long cultural visit. It helps reset the pace and fits errands, food, or a short meeting.</string>
    <string name="shopping_3_title">Flagman</string>
    <string name="shopping_3_description">A central shopping option that is easy to include in a downtown itinerary.</string>
    <string name="shopping_3_detail">Flagman is useful when you do not want to leave the center but still need an indoor stop. It pairs naturally with nearby landmarks and evening plans.</string>
    <string name="shopping_4_title">Aksion</string>
    <string name="shopping_4_description">A recognizable city shopping location suited for a mixed-purpose visit.</string>
    <string name="shopping_4_detail">Add Aksion when you want the route to stay flexible. It works for a quick indoor block between walks, especially if the weather changes or the schedule compresses.</string>
    <string name="shopping_5_title">MOLL Matritsa</string>
    <string name="shopping_5_description">A large modern shopping and entertainment center with stores, food options, and family activities.</string>
    <string name="shopping_5_detail">Choose MOLL Matritsa when you need a larger and more predictable indoor stop with retail, cafes, cinema, and family leisure in one place. It works well for a longer indoor part of the route.</string>
</resources>
